Guide to the American Institute of Planners Records, 1934-1978
American Institute of Planners Records, 1934-1978
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
American Institute of Planners Records, 1934-1978
4007
American Institute of Planners
83.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, bylaws, policy statements, contracts, proposals, bills and receipts, publications, drafts, articles, reviews, surveys, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Primarily files of American Institute of Planners executive offices, departments, and committees, this collection consists of correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, bylaws, policy statements, contracts, proposals, bills and receipts, publications by AIP and other organizations, drafts, articles, reviews, surveys, and other materials relating to the activities of AIP and its local chapters. Subjects represented include educational and career opportunites for women and minorities in planning; grants and fellowships; continuing education; planning awards; AIP annual meetings; AIP conferences (including talks as well as files); AIP's 50th anniversary; AIP membership standards, registration, and role in the planning profession; certification of educational institutions offering degrees in planning; professional development; professional ethics; housing; regional planning; environmental issues; and related topics.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Primarily files of American Institute of Planners executive offices, departments, and committees, this collection consists of correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, bylaws, policy statements, contracts, proposals, bills and receipts, publications by AIP and other organizations, drafts, articles, reviews, surveys, and other materials relating to the activities of AIP and its local chapters. Included are materials pertaining to the National Membership Standards Committee, the National Student Steering Committee, and other AIP committees; AIP departments, especially the Planning Education Department; the National Planning Board and its successors, the National Resources Board (1934) and the National Resources Committee (1935); the Planning Foundation of America and the AIP Foundation; the American Society of Planning Officials, which shared many programs with AIP until their merger in 1978 as the American Planning Association; the Department of Housing and Urban Development, Environmental Protection Agency, and other government agencies; the Association of Collegiate Schools of Planning; Planners for Equal Opportunity; Aid to Minority Planning Students; Advocate Planners; Planners Roll Call; and many other organizations active in planning and related fields.
Subjects represented include educational and career opportunites for women and minorities in planning; grants and fellowships; continuing education; planning awards; AIP annual meetings; AIP conferences (including talks as well as files); AIP's 50th anniversary; AIP membership standards, registration, and role in the planning profession; certification of educational institutions offering degrees in planning; professional development; professional ethics; housing; regional planning; environmental issues; and related topics.
First day cover (stamp) for the 50th Anniversary of the American Institute of Planners, 1967.
Includes three 16 mm films.
SUBJECTS
Names:
American Institute of Planners.; American Institute of Planners. National Membership Standards Committee.; American Institute of Planners. National Student Steering Committee.; American Institute of Planners. Planning Education Dept.; American Institute of Planners Foundation.; American Society of Planning Officials.; Association of Collegiate Schools of Planning.; Planners for Equal Opportunity.; Planning Foundation of America.; United States. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development.; United States. Environmental Protection Agency.; United States. National Resources Committee.
Titles:
Planners roll call.
Subjects:
City planning.; College students--Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Environmental policy.; Housing policy.; Minorities--Education.; Planners.; Planning education.; Professional ethics.; Regional planning.; Resource allocation.; Universities and colleges--Accreditation.; Women--Education.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
See also: Guide to the American Society of Planning Officials Records ( collection #3247) and the Guide to the American Planning Association Records ( collection #4075).
SERIES LIST
Series I. General AIP Files
Boxes 1-76, 84
Series II. ASPO-Ford Foundation Fellowship Program
Boxes 76-78
Series III. Applications from universities with planning programs for AIP recognition
Box 79
Series IV. Publications
Box 80-83
Series V. Films
F-1620-1622
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. General AIP Files
  - National resources planning, Board publication, National Resources Committee, 1934-1943 (Box 1)
  - National resources planning, Board publications, National Resources Committee, 1934-1943 (Box 2)
  - National resources planning, Board publications, National Resources Committee, 28 tapes (Box 3)
  - AIP Conference papers #001-084 (see index first folder) (Box 4)
  - AIP Conference papers #086-128, 1970 (Box 5)
  - AIP Conference files, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
  - AIP Conference papers #55-102, 1971 (Box 7-8)
  - AIP Conference papers #39-64 (see index first folder), 1972 (Box 8)
  - AIP Conference papers #65-95, AIP Conference papers #5-41 (see index first folder), 1972,1973 (Box 9)
  - AIP Conference papers #42-87, 1973 (Box 9-10)
  - AIP Conference papers #88-139, AIP Conference papers #141-187, 1973 (Box 10)
  - AIP Conference papers #1-805 (see index first folder), 1974 (Box 11-12)
  - AIP, 1953-1964
    - Board of Government meeting (Box 12)
    - Annual Conferences (Box 12)
    - Newsletters (Box 12)
    - By-Laws (Box 12)
    - 36th Annual Meeting (Box 12)
    - Membership, 1953-1956 (Box 12)
  - Board of Governance: Minutes, Reports, Meetings, 1935-1977 (Box 13)
  - Journal of the American Institute of Planners
    - J.C. Nichols. Biographies, 1949 (Box 14)
    - Files on the Joint Committee on the National Capitol, 1943-1963 (Box 14)
  - "The Content of Professional Curricula in Planning", 1948 (Box 84)
  - "Statement of Policy on Urban Development and Expansion", 1950 (Box 84)
  - AIP Committee Council (Box 14-15)
  - New Committee Task Force, International Education for Environmental Design, Task Force & files, Other Misc., 1958-1972 (Box 15-16)
  - "New Communities Task Force","International Education for Environmental Design", Task Force & other misc. files, 1958-1972 (Box 17)
  - Chapter & Committee Reports & Newsletters (Box 17-18)
  - Archives, 1954-1975
    - AIP Chapter Presidents (Box 18, 19, 20)
    - Correspondence General newsletters (Box 18, 19, 20)
  - Confidential files, code of professional responsibility, 1972-1974 (Box 20, 21)
  - Correspondence memos, office files, 1966-1969 (Box 22, 23)
  - Correspondence reports, memos, 1968 (Box 23)
  - AIP publications, 1958 (Box 24)
  - The Journal of the American Institute of Planners, 1935-1959 (Box 25)
  - The Journal of the American Institute of Planners, 1960-1973 (Box 26)
  - Archives Misc. (Box 27)
  - AIP files, internship program, monthly membership, memos, equal opportunity, code of professional responsibility, policy finance, 1969-1972 (Box 27, 28)
  - AIP Misc. papers, 1969-1973 (Box 28, 29, 30)
  - Confidential Code of Professional Conduct, August 21, 1970 (Box 31)
  - Jury of Awards (Box 32, 33)
  - Budget, Board of Governors, AIP Awards, 1969-1978 (Box 34, 35)
  - Joyner Files (Box 36, 37)
  - Irving Hand, AIP Board of Governors Activities (Box 37, 38)
  - Miscellaneous Files, 1974 (Box 39)
  - Confidential Code of Professional Conduct, August 20, 1970 (Box 40)
  - Files of the Executive Director's Office, 1970-1974 (Box 41)
  - Tapes, Films, and Other, Conference, 1974 (Box 42,43)
  - Irving Hand, AIP Board of Governors, 1965-1969 (Box 43, 44, 45)
  - Confidential Code of Professional Conduct (Box 45, 46)
  - Conference Papers #1-230, #1-142, 1975 (Box 46)
  - Conference Papers #143-230, 1975 (Box 47)
  - AIP Papers, Proceedings of 50th Anniversary Convention AIP Papers, 1943-1967 (Box 47, 48)
  - Conference Papers #232-503, #1-25, 1975-1977 (Box 49)
  - Conference Proceedings, 1971 (Box 49, 50)
  - Minute Supplement Book, Correspondence (Box 51)
  - Miscellaneous Technical Department Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 52)
  - Technical Department Mailing, Metropolitan & Regional Planning Departments, Information Systems Department, Planning Education Dept., Urban Design Dept. Environmental Planning Dept., Transportation Planning Dept., City Planning & Management Dept., State Planning Dept., 1975 (Box 53)
  - Department Mailing, 1974-1976 (Box 53)
  - AIP Program, Board Meeting and Executive Committee Meeting, Program and Budget Task Force & Approved Budgets, 1974-1976 (Box 54)
  - Executive Director's Personal File, 1975 (Box 55)
  - Technical Department Mailings, 1976 (Box 56)
  - Early By-Laws of various chapters of the American Institute of Planners (3" ltr.), 1968-1978 (Box 57)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) 72-1 - contract/budget (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
  - EPA/ESD (Environmental Studies Division) activities (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Billings (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - EPA 801375 - draft for final review, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - EPA I - drafts (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - EPA I - working committee correspondence (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Towards a Comprehensive Plan for Environmental Quality - Ian L. McHarg, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - The Comprehensive Plan and Environmental Quality - AIP (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Draft of final report 72-1 - originals (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - EPA consultant selection procedure (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - EPA sub-contractor information (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - EPA comprehensive environmental plan (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - EPA 72-1 - historical development (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - North Carolina study, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - EOA 72-1 draft - Wallace, McHarg, Roberts & Todd, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 16-19)
  - EPA grant - proposal and budget (Box 58, Folder 20-22)
  - EPA 72-1 - AIP advisory group (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - EPA R-801375 - meeting expense reports (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - EPA/ESD - work program (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - EPA 72-1 - statement of work (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - EPA 72-1 - policy papers (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - EPA 72-1 - project papers (Box 58, Folder 28-29)
  - EPA 72-1 - advisory group meeting, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - EPA 72-1 - advisory group meeting, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - EPA - minutes of advisory group meeting, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - EPA time sheets - T. Mann (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - EPA 72-1 - time sheets (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - EPA 72-1 - bibliography (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - EPA 72-1 - general correspondence (Box 58, Folder 36-37)
  - Comments from Peter House on February Progress Report (Box 58, Folder 38-39)
  - EPA - Progress Report, February 1973 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - EPA project - progress reports, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - EPA - R 801375 report outline draft, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - EPA 72-1 - AIP advisory group mailing No. 1, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - EPA mailing No. 2, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Summary (Box 58, Folder 45-46)
  - The Comprehensive Plan and the Environmental Impact Statement Process, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - National Conference on Urban Environment, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - Technology and Governance Conference - AIP Representatives (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - "Development of National Extension Program in Urban and Regional Planning" (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - "A Proposal to Design Curriculum and Training Program for the Training of Mid-career Women" - Comprehensive (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - "Design of Model Curricula and Training Techniques - Sub-professional Manpower Development" (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - AIP - Non-metro Planning Research (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - AIP Land Use Planning - information exchange (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - EPA - Quarles meeting (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - An Environmental Training System (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Chronological file -, April 1978 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Chronological file -, Mar. 1978 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Chronological file -, February 1978 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Chronological file -, February 1978 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Chronological file -, January 1978 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Planning Foundation of America (PFA) Expenditures (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - PFA general correspondence (Box 59, Folder 14-16)
  - PFA - bank account, treasurer, auditor (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - PFA chronological file, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - PFA - The Foundation Center (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - PFA Board of Directors Meeting, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Memorial grants made to PFA (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Grant from Rockefeller Brothers for editing videotapes (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - PFA recreation (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - PFA membership, Board of Directors (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - PFA minutes (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - PFA, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - National Recreation and Parks Association (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - PFA/Foundation, 1960-1965 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - AIP: memo regarding tax exemption, memo tax status, 1943-1959 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Certificate of incorporation - document 1 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Proposed by-laws - document 2 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - "A Detailed Statement of Proposed Activities" - document 3 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - AIP - Foundation program study (Box 59, Folder 34-35)
  - Confer-In - negotiations, program, etc., 1970 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - ASPO publications, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - ASPO publications, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - AIP group insurance plan and related materials (Box 59, Folder 39-42)
  - "Successful Organization - A Guide of A.I.A. Officers and Members" (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Conference - meetings of other organizations, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 44-45)
  - San Juan (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Speakers - Atlanta conference (Box 59, Folder 47-48)
  - Audio-visual (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Reception - conference committee, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 50)
  - Tours and tips - conference committee, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Minutes of PFA, 1965-1972 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - PFA - "Modelling Recreation Use in a Metropolitan Region" (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Requests for documents (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Reports to Board (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Quarterly progress reports (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Subcontracts and requisitions (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - PFA (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - "Modeling Recreation Use in a Metropolitan Region" (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - HUD - PFA contract no. D.C. PD-19 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Cost control statements (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Aid to Minority Planning Students (AMPS) (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Federal City College (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - California State Polytechnic (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - University of Cincinnati (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Michigan State University (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - University of Illinois (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - University of Virginia (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - University of Washington (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - "Guide to Planning Practice" - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) contract, 1976-1977 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - EPA 72-1 contract and budget (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Planning and Development Collaborative International (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - "Guide to Planning Practice" - invitations (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - EPA I - contract #R 801375 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Contract - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - EPA advisory group - expenses (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - "Guide to Planning Practice"; NEA contract, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - NEA contract 10/7504 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Schools' reports, 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 30-33)
  - AMPS fund raising campaign (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - AMPS programs - miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - PFA Equal Opportunity proposal (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - PFA - annual report for foreign and domestic non-profit corporations (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Proposal writing session, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 38-39)
  - AMPS chapter report (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - AIP tax exempt status (Box 60, Folder 41-42)
  - AIP Foundation (Box 60, Folder 43)
  - PFA background materials (Box 60, Folder 44)
  - PFA Board of Directors meeting, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 45)
  - PFA Ford Foundation grant, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 46)
  - PFA proposal (Box 60, Folder 47)
  - PFA's tax-exemption and annual reports (Box 60, Folder 48)
  - PFA (Box 60, Folder 49-50)
  - District of Columbia annual report (Box 60, Folder 51)
  - PFA treasurer's report (Box 60, Folder 52)
  - PFA chronological file, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 53)
  - AIP new tax law (Box 60, Folder 54)
  - PFA reports to Board of Directors (Box 60, Folder 55)
  - Meetings (Box 60, Folder 56)
  - Resolution approving the project (Box 60, Folder 57)
  - AMPS - summary report (Box 60, Folder 58)
  - AMPS solicitation report #1 by Gerald R. Mylroie (Box 60, Folder 59)
  - AMPS solicitation and pledge reports (Box 60, Folder 60)
  - AMPS solicitation and pledge reports (Box 61, Folder 1-3)
  - Project documents (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - PFA minutes and agenda (also draft minutes) (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - PFA Board meeting (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Allocation of grant funds (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - PFA receipts or bills (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) contract - PFA no. 1: "Estimating Recreation Demand" (Box 61, Folder 9-10)
  - PFA contract with HUD (Box 61, Folder 11-13)
  - AIP (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Proposal (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Publication for AIP/National Recreation and Park Administration (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - AIP/NRPA joint committee (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Background materials (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Consad Research Corporation (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - "An Annotated Bibliography: Outdoor Recreation Demand Literature" (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Code of professional responsibility - ethics (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Chronological file, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Academy for Contemporary Problems (Box 61, Folder 23-24)
  - Minority relations (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - United States Department of the Interior (DOI)/United States Geological Survey/Land Classification System (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT) workshops - general (Box 61, Folder 27-28)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)/AIP workshops (Box 61, Folder 29-31)
  - Census Bureau (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - HUD - Nonmetro Growth Conference (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - The Inter-agency Rating Panel (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Related job descriptions, qualification and classification (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - HUD/AIP/USDA Paper (Box 61, Folder 36-37)
  - HUD Intergovernmental personnel and training handbook/intergovernmental training matters (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - HUD housing guidelines (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - State County City Service Center (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Proposed originals (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - HUD Biennial Design Awards Workshop, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 42-43)
  - Community planner (020) (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Community Development Service (Box 61, Folder 45-46)
  - AIP/Extension Conference (Box 61, Folder 47)
  - AIP/USDA Extension Conference - participants (Box 61, Folder 48)
  - HUD fellowships/work study (Box 61, Folder 49)
  - Status of "Planners in the Federal Government" (Box 61, Folder 50)
  - Status of "Planners in the Federal Government" (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
  - Advocacy Planning (Box 62, Folder 3-4)
  - Technical Department Council Meetings, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Technical Department Council Meetings, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Technical Department Council Meetings, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Technical Department Council Meetings, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Status of Planners (020) (Box 62, Folder 9-10)
  - Career guidance brochure written by Ralph Hirsch (paid by Automotive Safety Foundation), 1970 (Box 62, Folder 11-12)
  - Cooperative Extension Service (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - HEW (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - HUD (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - AMPS/special gifts (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - AMPS/kits (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - AMPS/solicitation responses (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - AMPS/press release information (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - AMPS/solicitation of students (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - AMPS school survey, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - School memoranda (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Planning Education Policy - state (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Recognition - degree programs (Box 62, Folder 24-26)
  - Recognition - budget (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - National Education Development Committee, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - "Planners and the Planning Profession" (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Manpower (Box 62, Folder 30-31)
  - Land speculation (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Advocate Planners issues (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Advocate Planners responses (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Advocate Planners- property tax (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - AP 71-1 - remedies to exclusionary land use practices (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Baltimore Advocacy project (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Baltimore information (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Advocate Planners (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Advocacy of poor and minority interests (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Advocate Planners (Box 62, Folder 41-45)
  - Clean Water Act (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Complex source (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Flood plain planning and management (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Growth control techniques (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Grant programs (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Graphics (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Speaking engagements (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Solid waste education (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Public relations - TV (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Noise (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Health planning (Box 63, Folder 11-12)
  - Environmental education (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Doctorate in planning (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Responses to John Friedmann's article (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Clean Air Act and land use (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Air pollution (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Social planning (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Education planning (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Engineering contracts (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Comprehensive day care planning (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Department of Labor report (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Criminal justice planning (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Planning and cable TV (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Mid-career Training Demonstration Program - Department of Agriculture Extension Service (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Jobs (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Study of profession (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Careers for women (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Memoranda to persons interested in planning as a profession (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Guidance counseling including books - high school (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Career guidance information (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Career guidance information brochure (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Career guidance - urban and regional (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Planners in law (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Minority planners in AIP (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Planners for Equal Opportunity (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Minority Placement Conference (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Black Planning Network (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - National Education Development Committee annual report, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - National Education Development Committee correspondence (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Planning Education (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Planning Education Task Force (Box 63, Folder 42-45)
  - National Forum on Growth Policy - AIP (Box 63, Folder 46)
  - "How to Solicit" (Box 63, Folder 47)
  - AMPS schedule (Box 63, Folder 48)
  - AMPS thank you letters (Box 63, Folder 49)
  - AMPS - printout return inventory (Box 63, Folder 50)
  - AMPS accounting (Box 63, Folder 51)
  - AMPS corporate solicitation (Box 63, Folder 52)